That was one awful nightmare you showed me.
You deserved it.
As a dragon, you used the
hero to give up your life
and abandoned the people, the gods,
the other dragons, and me.
And now you're living a peaceful
life like nothing happened?!
You're right.
I had given up on life.
But it's different now.
After being reborn as a human,
my parents, fellow villagers,
Celina, Chris...
They all helped me realize...
that I lacked the resolve to live
during my dragon life.
Resolve?
To swear that you'll face any and all
difficulties without ever backing down.
And now I have it.
Hah, what the heck?
What exactly did you swear
to yourself, Dolly?
Isn't it obvious?
I swore to live my life, as a human
with a dragon soul, to the fullest.
Bring on all the despair and
difficulties in the world.
I am not about to back down,
not a single step.
You're so cool.
But this is my world, you know?
You're not going back without a fight!
It's that crazy, evil dragon that gave you
and the hero so much trouble! Say he...
...llo?
You may think this is a game,
but I cannot stand the sight of that thing.
Now die.
Huh? No way! Wait, timeout!
I'm sowwy!
Hello, Human Life
This is all wrong!
You were supposed to be
weaker after rebirth!
And I didn't hold back one bit!
Excuse me for being in a
murderous rage after that nightmare.
But this strength will only
last me through this life.
Should I be reborn again,
my soul may degrade.
The curse of the fallen gods, huh?
They put a nasty reincarnation curse on you.
And after several of those,
my soul is sure to perish.
Oh... So you'll be gone eventually,
even if I do nothing.
What's this? I thought you'd be dancing for joy.
Meanie! I really do think of you
as a dear friend, you know?
Look, even you've let me off the hook here.
You have performed much
evil as a fallen god,
but at the same time,
you're my one and only arch-nemesis—
friend.
See? You do get it!
Well, bye. I'll come again to play with you!
You overslept again?
Well, I had a bad dream.
One that tired me out.
By the way, Celina,
what would you do if you encountered
armored bears during a hunt?
Huh? Er...
I'll use my cursed eyes to send them home.
Fighting would be dangerous for both of us.
What? Why are you laughing?
Welcome!
Chris, may I ask you something?
Sure. What's up?
I've decided to enroll in
Galoa's magic academy.
Oh?
Mind telling me what brought this on?
I had a dream.
A dream about the end of Verun Village.
A dream?
It was weirdly realistic.
I don't want to lose this village.
There are too many people I hold dear here.
And that thought reminded
me of what Denzel said.
If you want to protect the village you love,
leaving it might be one way to do it.
Ah.
I want to gain new knowledge
at the magic academy
and rethink how to take the village forward.
I think I could help make this
a better place that way.
What do you say?
That sounds great.
I would love to have a friend
like you to learn with.
I appreciate your saying that.
I'll ask the headmistress about the
paperwork for the entrance exam.
Let's make a toast.
Miu! Another mug of milk, please!
Sure! Coming right up!
Dolan's going to leave the village?
You've finally made your decision, huh?
Take care.
I'm just going to take the exam.
I'll be right back.
Good luck.
I'm off.
That answer is several generations old.
Are you sure about this, Dolly?
Why are you here, Kalavith?
Why am I here? Duh.
For love!
Just kidding!
I'm in the middle of an exam here.
This stuff is a piece of cake for you.
You finished right away and took a nap.
Wrong. I was meditating.
Examinee Dolan!
Sleeping during the exam?
You must be confident.
Mister Alister, I wasn't sleeping.
If you're done, we can
stop wasting time here.
You'll have practicals tomorrow.
Do your best so you have no regrets.
Dolan must be in the middle of his exam now.
The magic academy, huh? He's awesome.
Unlike someone we know.
Shut it, you shrimp!
Wha?!
Quiet! The monsters will hear us coming!
Sowwy...
Sorry.
Up the pace, Celina.
Huh? A monster? I'm ready to fight.
Evil snake that binds my soul...
Afflict my foes with your curse!
Wait, Celina! We haven't run into any yet!
Jalaam!
Check if we have any casualties!
I'm sorry! I'm so sorry!
Don't worry. It's just a scratch.
Celina's been down lately.
Was she that hurt by Dolan's decision
to go to the magic academy?
Why doesn't she just go with them, then?
Ow.
You may have forgotten,
but lamia are feared as man-eating monsters.
You heard about how people on the
streets of Galoa feared her, right?
It'd be impossible to take
her to the academy.
So, if Dolan enrolls in the magic academy...
He won't be back for two years.
And he might get a job in town and stay.
Celina's one thing,
but are you okay with that?
Lay off!
Because Dolan taught me how to
read this country's language,
I can now read picture books
like these by myself.
He'll probably learn lots at the
academy and become a fine mage.
All to help the village.
He really is amazing.
I want to go with him, but...
A lamia?!
Come here! She's dangerous!
I'm a lamia.
I'd only hinder his dream if I went along.
It's fine. I was on a journey
to find a husband, anyway.
The lamia tradition where we find a husband
and have them come to our village...
I need to uphold that first.
Dolan!
Oh... So I was in love with him.
I didn't realize I wanted him to be with me
and come to the lamia village with me.
But I also want him to prioritize
his love for Verun Village.
I can't make him ignore this
place because of how I feel.
Life would've been so amazing
if I could be with him..
I had so much fun in Verun.
Kept you waiting?
Denzel.
I heard you finished the
written exam in no time.
I'm looking forward to seeing
you here as a student.
Hey, we don't know that I passed yet.
By the way, Denzel,
there's something I want to ask you.
Celina, do you have a moment?
I have some news for you.
Celina?
"To the Villagers." "To Dolan"?
Hello, Dolan.
Uh, is this how you're
supposed to start a letter?
How was the exam?
I'm sure you would say,
"Hmph. Not a problem," like you usually do.
Er, I apologize for leaving
the village so suddenly.
Seeing you take a step forward
got me all motivated as well.
I've decided to restart
my search for a husband.
I didn't have the heart
to say goodbye in person,
so I'm leaving this letter.
Thank you for everything, Dolan.
I'm really glad I got to meet
you and live in Verun Village.
To my beloved Dolan.
From Celina.
Celina!
What is that?
I've never seen anything like it!
A demon?!
But we closed the portal.
Is that a dragon,
like the ones Dolan mentioned?
Celina!
Dolan's here! This is so awkward!
Is this...
Oh, this takes me back.
This is where we first met.
Yeah, I still remember it
like it was yesterday.
Your seduction dance was so cute.
Grr! That's insulting!
Look, Celina!
Wow.
Are those earth elementals?
The lizards aren't back yet, huh?
Even though the area is calm now,
moving back here can't be easy.
We only first met recently,
but it feels like forever ago.
Same here.
I made so many memories,
all because of you.
Thank you.
Dolan, I'm so glad I came to Verun.
Sorry for suddenly deciding
to join the academy.
I should've talked to you about it first.
I'm sorry, too. I tried to leave the
village without telling anyone.
When I was there for the exam, I asked...
And I found out that students
may bring familiars with them.
You need to form a pact,
but once that's done,
they can even bring monsters to the academy.
If you wouldn't mind,
would you please come with me?
I can... go?
I can go with Dolan?
You don't get it!
Lamia are man-eating monsters!
Do you know what people will think of you
if you walk around with a monster in tow?!
What about the teachers and
other students at the academy?
They won't think kindly of you!
You'll never make any friends!
If anyone badmouths you,
I'll deal with them.
That's even worse!
Are you okay?!
You're going to become a fine mage,
gain power and influence,
and help the village, right?
Then you mustn't cause any problems.
You can't take me along.
If anything happens in town,
we can work on it together.
And I don't mind if I don't make
any friends in the academy!
I want to see a new world with you!
Okay!
Me, too... I wadda go with you, too.
Mm. I passed.
Yes!
Congratulations.
In the name of the
God of Contracts La Warter,
I hereby pronounce a true and binding
pact formed between you two.
That symbolizes that you have
formed a familiar pact.
Wow... So this is the symbol of our bond.
Christina.
We leave Dolan and Celina in your hands.
Sure.
Don't follow any strangers.
I'll keep it in mind.
I'll take care of your home, brother!
Good luck living alone, Marco.
Celina.
Yes?
I...
I'll be joining the magic
academy next year, too.
Take care of Dolan until then.
Got it.
We should go.
We can't be here chatting all day.
Thank you all for coming to see us off.
Giddy-up!
If anything happens, I'll come rushing
back from the academy, I promise!
Don't get sick! Don't get hurt!
Please be well until I return!
See you later!
Once we reach Galoa, you'll be
busy with the enrolling procedures.
You won't have time to feel sad.
Right.
Are the students there nice?
Will we have to deal with
any scary seniors?
Don't worry. If anyone dares bully
you two, I'll deal with them.
Dolan's and my new life is about to begin.
I'll always be with him.
It feels like a dream come true.
Now we can be lovers and...
Lovers?
Huh?
I want to see a new world with you!
Was that...
not a declaration of love?!
Oh, yeah. I'd like to visit your
village sometime too, Celina.
Huh?
If you could stay with me and not get sick
of me until then, I'd appreciate it.
Of course!